Zulfa H Rajabu

kimzux0718@gmail.com |+255783548837|LinkedIn Link: https://www.linkedin.com/in/zulfa-

rajabu-9420461a4/

Address: Dar-es-salaam, Tanzania

PROFILE

My primary goal is to apply my technical expertise all throughout the full software life cycle to

ensure production and delivery of products and services that meet client specifications. Along

with a competent software developing team, and with strong personal knowledge, skills, and a

little experience in software engineering, I am positive that this goal can be achieved. My

experience as entry level software developer enhanced my abilities in designing and

implementing. One of my objectives is to keep updated with the latest IT trends and

technologies. I am confident that if given the opportunity, I can be a useful talent to the

company.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Html

CSS

JavaScript

• React is

• Php, laravel framework

• Git

Mysql

EDUCATION

Women Techsters Fellowship,

Lagos, Nigeria

Tech4dev

August 2022 - present

Bachelor of Computer Engineering,

Dar-salaam, Tanzania

Dar-es-salaam Institute of Technology

2017 - 2021

A Levels, Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry

Tabora, Tanzania

Tabora Girls

2015 - 2017

PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

Software developer Field Trainee/TYD

innovation incubator, Dar-es-salaam,

Sep 2019 - Sep 2020

- Performed problem initiated, data collection, gathering requirement for functional and non functional requirements.
- System design that involve database design using laravel schema that found in laravel framework.
- Develop the landing page using CSS, HTML and Javascript.
- Conduct the system analysis to obtain he details that will help in getting data and details required for the system design.

Software Developer Internship/ Inets Company Limited, Dar-es-salaam

Sep 2020 - Nov 2020

- Collaborate with a team member build online documentation.
- Develop the online document by using CSS, HTML, also PHP for the database.
- Design the form by using the figma and also using adobe xd, after that code it using HTML CSS and Javascript.

Software Developer Intern Thinkmate Limited, Dar-es-salaam

April 2022 - Present

- Develop Human Resource Management System in php with laravel framework with bootstrap for the frontend.
- Database Design for the systems by using Mysql Workbench together with laravel schema.
- Developed technical specifications and coding documentations for new projects.
- Addressed technical queries from clients in a prompt manner
- Participated in creating project plan and release plan.
- Coordinated with project team to develop ad-hoc prototypes.

REFERENCES:

Senorine Michael Dar-es-salaam, Tanzania Mobile: +25574710970 [semichael@ark.co.tz] Christopher Shoo Dar-es-salaam, Tanzania Mobile: +255738223987 [rishaelbenson@gmail.com]